Kush Bhatnagar

Wilson Garden, Bangalore 🏫

+91-9886298777

kushbhatnagar86@gmail.com

/in/kushbhatnagar/ in

kushbhatnagar.github.io/

I am an MLOps Engineer with around 13 years of professional experience. I have experience in Machine Learning, Natural Language Processing, Amazon Web Service, DevOps, Test Automation Framework development, Performance Test, and Agile Methodologies. Currently, I am developing a Cloud platform for CI-CD pipelines of end-to-end Machine learning Projects. I am a certified AWS Solution Architect and AWS Machine Learning Specialist.

Skills

- ML frameworks (TensorFlow, PyTorch, Keras, Scikit-Learn, Spark-ML)
- AWS- SageMaker Studio, S3, EC2, EKS, ECR, Kinesis, Glue, VPC, Dynamo DB, EMR, Athena
- Kubernetes, Docker
- DVC
- CVAT

- FastAPI, Flask
- Python
- Java
- MLFlow, Kubeflow
- BentoML, KFServing
- GIT, Jenkins
- Selenium, JMeter
- Cucumber

Experience

11/2016 - PRESENT

ML Ops Engineer / HP Inc, Bangalore

Project: HP ePrint is a cloud-based print solution that provides a unique print experience to the office, home, and large format customers. The Print cloud platform has more than 60 million print consumers are connected and uses various capabilities of the platform

- Developing Docker and Kubernetes pipelines for Model deployment, Serving, and Monitoring
- Automated End to End Data Versioning process in DVC and CVAT
- Working on Proof of Concepts on ML related AWS Services like SageMaker Studio to determine the feasibility of using a particular service for a business use case
- Working on pan HP initiative to harvest, develop, and establish practices for developing, deploying, and maintaining ML solutions in production
- Created a utility to select Regression Test Cases using Classification Learning Models
- Worked on various Machine Learning Proof of Concepts to enhance existing Test Automation Methodologies
- Developed API Automation Framework and integrate with Jenkins for CI-CD pipeline

11/2012 - 10/2016

Senior QA Engineer / JDA Software, Bangalore

Project: The Agile Business Process Platform (ABPP) is a framework allowing for the design, development, and configuration of data models and workflows that incorporate complex business logic. It is a complete end-to-end development and run-time environment for developing, customizing, configuring, and running supply chain applications.

- Developed Page Object Model-based UI Automation framework in Selenium and Java for functional test cases.
- Created and executed automated software test plans, cases, and scripts to uncover, identify, and document problems and their causes
- Implemented an Automation Regression suite in Quick Test Professional to catch issues in the early stages of development
- Led QA testing that involves the development of functional test cases against the requirement and communicates problems with the product owner that could adversely impact its value

07/2009 - 10/2012

Senior Software Engineer / Accenture, Bangalore

Project: Customer Segments-Inter Credit Decision Platform deals with customer requests for small business credit cards. The project's main objective is to decide the customer request based on different criteria

- Implemented an Automated Regression test suite in QTP to catch issues in the early stages of development
- Worked with different stakeholders, development, and business teams to interpret the complex requirements into test scenarios and test scripts
- Implemented Risk Based Testing to cope with the short testing cycles to prioritize the requirements

Education

08/2008

Bachelor of Engineering / Rajasthan University, Jaipur

Completed B.E in Information and Technology with Honours and a GPA of 3.5

Activities

I am an active participant on the Kaggle platform and currently an Expert in Notebooks and Discussion Categories. I have a penchant for technical writing, a few of my articles were published on Medium in various publications